
	{"category": "sports",
	 "questions": [
	 		{"question":"Which NHL Team are nicknamed the 'Coyotes'?", "answers": ["Calgary", "Vancouver", "Ottawa", "Arizona"], "correctAnswer": "Arizona"},
	 		{"question":"Which U.S. golfer stands second in the all-time list of major winners with thirteen titles?", "answers": ["Tiger Woods", "Tony Jacklin", "Bobby Jones", "Arnold Palmer"], "correctAnswer": "Bobby Jones"},
	 		{"question":"Chukkas is the term given to periods played in what sport?", "answers": ["Polo", "Ice Hockey", "Hockey", "Curling"], "correctAnswer": "Polo"},
	 		{"question":"How many goose feathers does it take to make a shuttlecock?", "answers": ["16", "60", "21", "32"], "correctAnswer": "16"},
	 		{"question":"In Olympic Archery, how far is the competitor from the target?", "answers": ["50m", "120m", "70m", "100m"], "correctAnswer": "70m"},
	 		{"question":"Terry Griffiths and Mark Williams are former Snooker World Champions. What nationality are they?", "answers": ["Welsh", "Scottish", "Australian", "English"], "correctAnswer": "Welsh"},
	 		{"question":"Who won the 2013 National Basketball Association (NBA) title?", "answers": ["LA Lakers", "Miami Heat", "Chicago Bulls", "San Antonio Spurs"], "correctAnswer": "Miami Heat"},
	 		{"question":"Which nation's Rugby Union team are known as the All Blacks?", "answers": ["Australia", "South Africa", "France", "New Zealand"], "correctAnswer": "New Zealand"},
	 		{"question":"The rider wearing the Red Polka Jersey in the Tour De France is called the 'King of the...'?", "answers": ["Tour", "France", "Race", "Mountain"], "correctAnswer": "Mountain"},
	 		{"question":"The brown ball is worth how many points in snooker?", "answers": ["2", "1", "4", "3"], "correctAnswer": "4"},
	 		{"question":"Maria Mednyanszky is a 5-time world champion in what sport?", "answers": ["Volleyball", "Table Tennis", "Tennis", "Ice Hockey"], "correctAnswer": "Table Tennis"},
	 		{"question":"In what year did Roger Bannister become the first man to run the mile in under 4 minutes?", "answers": ["1974", "1954", "1944", "1964"], "correctAnswer": "1954"},
	 		{"question":"In Greyhound racing, what number trap wears the black and white striped jacket?", "answers": ["6", "4", "5", "3"], "correctAnswer": "6"},
	 		{"question":"In which city do the Steelers compete in the NFL?", "answers": ["Denver", "Buffalo", "Washington", "Pittsburgh"], "correctAnswer": "Pittsburgh"},
	 		{"question":"What position does NHL hockey great Zdeno Chara play?", "answers": ["Goalie", "Defence", "Left Wing", "Center"], "correctAnswer": "Defence"},
	 		{"question":"In what sport would you use a sloop or a cutter?", "answers": ["Sailing", "Snooker", "Bob sledding", "Skiing"], "correctAnswer": "Sailing"},
	 		{"question":"Which famous person is credited with the term 'Caddie'?", "answers": ["John Ball", "Mary Queen of Scots", "Jim Barnes", "Ben Hogan"], "correctAnswer": "Mary Queen of Scots"},
	 		{"question":"When was the first baseball game televised?", "answers": ["1952", "1963", "1939", "1946"], "correctAnswer": "1939"},
	 		{"question":"Who won the men's gold medal in figure skating at the 2006 Olympic Games?", "answers": ["Alexei Kulik", "Evgeni Plushenko", "Elvis Stojko", "Victor Petrenko"], "correctAnswer": "Evgeni Plushenko"},
	 		{"question":"In which sport would you hear the terms basket, edge and crud?", "answers": ["Archery", "Swimming", "NASCAR", "Skiing"], "correctAnswer": "Skiing"},
	 		{"question":"Which football great was nicknamed 'The Gunslinger'?", "answers": ["Jay Cutler", "John Elway", "Jake Plummer", "Brett Farve"], "correctAnswer": "Brett Farve"},
	 		{"question":"In which sport would you use the terms bull calf, high ton, hot toddy and oche?", "answers": ["table tennis", "Skating", "Darts", "Bowling"], "correctAnswer": "Darts"},
	 		{"question":"Which sport awards the Podoloff Cup?", "answers": ["Golf", "Baseball", "Tennis", "Basketball"], "correctAnswer": "Basketball"},
	 		{"question":"In the national football league, how many balls is the home team required to provide?", "answers": ["12", "24", "36", "18"], "correctAnswer": "24"},
	 		{"question":"Which sport would you play at Wimbledon?", "answers": ["Golf", "Horse Racing", "Archery", "Tennis"], "correctAnswer": "Tennis"},
	 		{"question":"O. J. Simpson played which sport?", "answers": ["Football", "Boxing", "Hockey", "Baseball"], "correctAnswer": "Football"},
	 		{"question":"If you were watching Nadia Comaneci, which sport would you be watching?", "answers": ["Tennis", "Skiing", "Gymnastics", "Skating"], "correctAnswer": "Gymnastics"},
	 		{"question":"What is Edson Arantes do Nascimento better known as?", "answers": ["Mugsy", "Pele", "Ocho", "Cinco"], "correctAnswer": "Pele"},
	 		{"question":"In 1949, at the world hockey championship, Denmark was beaten 47 to 0. Who were they playing?", "answers": ["Canada", "America", "Russia", "Iceland"], "correctAnswer": "Canada"},
	 		{"question":"If you were watching Elvis Stojko compete, what sport would you be watching?", "answers": ["Figure Skating", "Tennis", "Golf", "Boxing"], "correctAnswer": "Figure Skating"},
	 		{"question":"How long is a tennis court?", "answers": ["102", "78", "50", "80"], "correctAnswer": "78"},
	 		{"question":"How many throwing events are there at the Olympic Games?", "answers": ["7", "2", "4", "8"], "correctAnswer": "4"},
	 		{"question":"How many points is a field goal worth in American football?", "answers": ["3", "4", "7", "6"], "correctAnswer": "3"},
	 		{"question":"Which of these events is one where men and women compete against each other at the Olympics?", "answers": ["Sailing", "Rowing", "Archery", "Tennis"], "correctAnswer": "Sailing"},
	 		{"question":"In a game of basketball how many players are on each side?", "answers": ["3", "5", "7", "6"], "correctAnswer": "5"},
	 		{"question":"In which sport would you see a scrum?", "answers": ["Soccer", "Rugby", "Cricket", "Rowing"], "correctAnswer": "Rugby"},
	 		{"question":"Yelena Isinbayeva has won five world championships. What sport does she compete in?", "answers": ["Pole Vault", "Gymnastics", "Long Jump", "High Jump"], "correctAnswer": "Pole Vault"},
	 		{"question":"Who won the women's team gymnastics at the 2012 Olympic Games?", "answers": ["Japan", "USA", "China", "Russia"], "correctAnswer": "USA"},
	 		{"question":"Who scored a perfect ten in gymnastics at the Olympic Games in Montreal?", "answers": ["Marta Egervari", "Nadia Comaneci", "Olga Korbut", "Debra Wilcox"], "correctAnswer": "Nadia Comaneci"},
	 		{"question":"Which country did runner Usian Bolt represent during 2012 Olympics?", "answers": ["America", "Bermuda", "Jamaica", "Kenya"], "correctAnswer": "Jamaica"},
	 		{"question":"Which throwing event provides athletes with a runway?", "answers": ["Discuss", "Javelin", "Hammer", "Shot Put"], "correctAnswer": "Javelin"},
	 		{"question":"What is the name of the NHL franchise in Calgary?", "answers": ["The Flames", "The Braves", "The Canadians", "The Canucks"], "correctAnswer": "The Flames"},
	 		{"question":"How old was golfer Morgan Pressel when she turned professional?", "answers": ["17", "24", "28", "14"], "correctAnswer": "17"},
	 		{"question":"In what year did Sarah Hughes win the gold medal in women's figure skating?", "answers": ["2002", "1980", "1994", "1988"], "correctAnswer": "2002"}	 			 			 			 	
		]
	}

	{"category": "history",
	 "questions": [
	 		{"question":"Conducted through the state of Georgia in 1864, who lead the 'March to the Sea'?", "answers": ["Sherman", "Jackson", "MacArther", "Custer"], "correctAnswer": "Sherman"},
	 		{"question":"Who was President of the United States during the war of 1812?", "answers": ["Polk", "Taft", "Jefferson", "Madison"], "correctAnswer": "Madison"},
	 		{"question":"Who was responsible for the Oklahoma City bombing on April 19, 1995?", "answers": ["Timothy McVeigh", "Eric Robert Rudolph", "Luke Helder", "Theodore Kaczynski"], "correctAnswer": "Timothy McVeigh"},
	 		{"question":"Which U.S. state was granted statehood on December 14th, 1819?", "answers": ["Alabama", "Georgia", "Kansas", "Ohio"], "correctAnswer": "Alabama"},
	 		{"question":"Which commoner became the head of England for 264 days?", "answers": ["Lord Mountbatten", "George Monck", "Guy Fawkes", "Richard Cromwell"], "correctAnswer": "Richard Cromwell"},
	 		{"question":"Where was the first skyscraper built in the United States?", "answers": ["New York", "Detroit", "Boston", "Chicago"], "correctAnswer": "Chicago"},
	 		{"question":"Who performed the first adult human heart transplant in 1967?", "answers": ["Dr. Christiaan Barnard", "Dr. Frederick Banting", "Dr. Alfred Blalock", "Dr. Charles Best"], "correctAnswer": "Dr. Christiaan Barnard"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following codenames represents a research and development project that produced the first atomic bombs during World War II?", "answers": ["The Philadelphia Experiment", "Barbarossa", "Operation Sea Lion", "The Manhatten Project"], "correctAnswer": "The Manhatten Project"},
	 		{"question":"Killing all 243 passengers and 16 crew members aboard, where did Pan Am Flight 103 explode?", "answers": ["Over the Pacific", "Over China", "The Alps", "Over Scotland"], "correctAnswer": "Over Scotland"},
	 		{"question":"Famous for defecting to the United States from Russia in 1967, who was Lana Peters?", "answers": ["Georgy Malenkov's daughter", "Stalin's daughter", "Vladimir Lenin's daughter", "Vasily Zaitsev's daughter"], "correctAnswer": "Stalin's daughter"},
	 		{"question":"In what year did WWI begin?", "answers": ["1867", "1914", "1812", "1939"], "correctAnswer": "1914"},
	 		{"question":"Where was the Fuhrer of Nazi Germany Adolf Hitler born?", "answers": ["Germany", "Russia", "France", "Austria"], "correctAnswer": "Austria"},
	 		{"question":"In which city was John F. Kennedy assassinated?", "answers": ["Dallas", "Chicago", "Washington DC", "Houston"], "correctAnswer": "Dallas"},
	 		{"question":"During which decade was the United States involved in the Korean War? ", "answers": ["1950s", "1980s", "1970s", "1960s"], "correctAnswer": "1950s"},
	 		{"question":"Taking place from 431 to 404 BC, who fought in the Peloponnesian wars?", "answers": ["Rome and Sparta", "Sparta and Athens", "Pisa and Rome", "Gaul and Athens"], "correctAnswer": "Sparta and Athens"},
	 		{"question":"Approximately, what percentage of the world's 1939 population was killed during World War II?", "answers": ["3%", "10%", "7%", "12%"], "correctAnswer": "3%"},
	 		{"question":"Code-named Operation Just Cause, which country did the United States invade in December of 1989?", "answers": ["Libya", "Costa Rica", "Iraq", "Panama"], "correctAnswer": "Panama"},
	 		{"question":"Which explorer was killed in Hawaii during his third exploratory voyage in 1779?", "answers": ["Ferdinand Magellan", "Marco Polo", "Christopher Columbus", "James Cook"], "correctAnswer": "James Cook"},
	 		{"question":"Taking place in 1951 during the Korean War, who became the first U.S. jet air ace in history?", "answers": ["John C. Meyer", "George Davis, Jr.", "James Jabara", "Joseph McConnell, Jr."], "correctAnswer": "James Jabara"},
	 		{"question":"Which King was taken prisoner by the Yorkists at the Battle of St. Albans during the War of the Roses in 1455?", "answers": ["King Henry VI", "King Henry VII", "King Henry IV", "King Henry V"], "correctAnswer": "King Henry VI"},
	 		{"question":"Historic Battles - Which of these battles occurred first?", "answers": ["Battle of Champion Hill", "Battle of Cross Keys", "Battle of Waterloo", "Battle of Solferino"], "correctAnswer": "Battle of Waterloo"},
	 		{"question":"British Prime Ministers - Which of the following Prime Ministers reigned the earliest?", "answers": ["Tony Blair", "David Cameron", "Gordon Brown", "John Major"], "correctAnswer": "John Major"},
	 		{"question":"Communication History - Which communication invention made its appearance first?", "answers": ["Telex Machines", "Telstar", "Video Recorder", "TV"], "correctAnswer": "TV"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the Ancient Wonders was destroyed by a fire in about 356 BC?", "answers": ["The Temple of Artemis", "The Temple of Artemis", "The Great Pyramid", "The Hanging Gardens of Babylon"], "correctAnswer": "The Temple of Artemis"},
	 		{"question":"William Pitt the Younger was Prime Minister during which of these events?", "answers": ["The French Revolution", "The Second World War", "The Hundred Year War", "The First World War"], "correctAnswer": "The French Revolution"},
	 		{"question":"Which country was once referred to as the Batavian Republic?", "answers": ["Austria", "Denmark", "Sweden", "The Netherlands"], "correctAnswer": "The Netherlands"},
	 		{"question":"Whom did Charles Guiteau assassinate in 1881?", "answers": ["John F. Kennedy", "Anwar Sadat", "James Garfield", "Louis Mountbatten"], "correctAnswer": "James Garfield"},
	 		{"question":"Fezzan, Cyrenaica and Tripolitania make up which modern country?", "answers": ["Angola", "Argentina", "Libya", "Sudan"], "correctAnswer": "Libya"},
	 		{"question":"Taking place from late November 2004 to January 2005, the Orange Revolution occurred in which nation?", "answers": ["Spain", "Ukraine", "Peru", "Hungary"], "correctAnswer": "Peru"},
	 		{"question":"What was President Ronald Reagan's codename while in office?", "answers": ["First Man", "The Eagle", "Rawhide", "Little Boy"], "correctAnswer": "Rawhide"},
	 		{"question":"Historical Trials - Which of these historical trials happened first?", "answers": ["Alfred Dreyfus", "Nicola Sacco", "OJ Simpson", "Nuremburg"], "correctAnswer": "Alfred Dreyfus"},
	 		{"question":"Who shot and killed Billy the Kid on July 14th, 1881?", "answers": ["Wild Bill Hickok", "Bat Masterson", "Wyatt Earp", "Pat Garrett"], "correctAnswer": "Pat Garrett"},
	 		{"question":"Which of these people won a Noble Peace Prize in 1978?", "answers": ["Margret Thatcher", "Jimmy Carter", "Anwar Sadat", "Pierre Trudeau"], "correctAnswer": "Anwar Sadat"},
	 		{"question":"Who was the mother of Queen Elizabeth I?", "answers": ["Mary I", "Catherine of Aragon", "Anne Boleyn", "Catherine the Great"], "correctAnswer": "Anne Boleyn"},
	 		{"question":"Who wrote a firsthand account of the Gallic Wars entitled 'Commentarii de Bello Gallico'?", "answers": ["Edgar Allen Poe", "Julius Caesar", "Jules Verne", "Mark Twain"], "correctAnswer": "Julius Caesar"},
	 		{"question":"Which ancient people were the first to use ships with sails?", "answers": ["Aztecs", "Incans", "Egyptians", "Vikings"], "correctAnswer": "Egyptians"},
	 		{"question":"Which nation was the first to grant women the right to vote?", "answers": ["Great Britian", "New Zealand", "America", "Canada"], "correctAnswer": "New Zealand"},
	 		{"question":"In 1918, Wilhelm II abdicated from which country?", "answers": ["Cuba", "Spain", "Mexico", "Germany"], "correctAnswer": "Germany"},
	 		{"question":"The Peloponnesian War was a battle between whom?", "answers": ["Sparta and Athens", "China and Nepal", "Argentina and Peru", "Spain and Portugal"], "correctAnswer": "Spain and Athens"}	 			 		
		]
	}	

	{"category": "entertainment",
	 "questions": [
	 		{"question":"How many pieces are on the board at the start of a game of chess?", "answers": ["28", "32", "36", "40"], "correctAnswer": "32"},
	 		{"question":"How many presidents of France had there been as at 2010?", "answers": ["7", "12", "23", "35"], "correctAnswer": "23"},
	 		{"question":"How many Horsemen of the Apocalypse feature in the Bible's Book of Revelation?", "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "500"], "correctAnswer": "4"},
	 		{"question":"New York City comprises how many boroughs?", "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "12"], "correctAnswer": "5"},
	 		{"question":"Which 19th century poet and novelist, when age twenty-six, married his thirteen year old cousin?", "answers": ["Edgar Allen Poe", "Oscar Wilde", "Victor Hugo", "William Shakespeare"], "correctAnswer": "Edgar Allen Poe"},
	 		{"question":"Which American city invented plastic vomit?", "answers": ["Chicago", "Detroit", "Columbus", "Baltimore"], "correctAnswer": "Chicago"},
	 		{"question":"In 'Ben Hur', which moderl thing can be seen during the chariot scene?", "answers": ["a telephone", "a car", "a streetlamp", "a waitress"], "correctAnswer": "a car"},
	 		{"question":"What was Karl Marx's favorite color", "answers": ["Brown", "Blue", "Red", "Purple"], "correctAnswer": "Red"},
	 		{"question":"Of the following, which was NOT the name of a Spice Girl?", "answers": ["Cutie", "Scary", "Sporty", "Baby"], "correctAnswer": "Cutie"},
	 		{"question":"The second best-selling album of the entire decade of 90s was a movie soundtrack. What was the movie?", "answers": ["Forrest Gump", "The Bodyguard", "Titanic", "The Lion King"], "correctAnswer": "The Bodyguard"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following band/artists has put out 3 of the top 10 best-selling albums of the 90s?", "answers": ["Backstreet Boys", "Metallica", "Garth Brooks", "Celine Dion"], "correctAnswer": "Garth Brooks"},
	 		{"question":"Who asked the musical question What if God was One of Us?", "answers": ["Sarah Mclachlan", "Sheryl Crow", "Joan Osborne", "Madonna"], "correctAnswer": "Joan Osborne"},
	 		{"question":"After Mother Love Bone's singer died of an overdose, 2 of it's member's formed which of the 90s most popular bands?", "answers": ["Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Nirvana", "Smashing Pumpkins", "Pearl Jam"], "correctAnswer": "Pearl Jam"},
	 		{"question":"Released New Year's Eve of 1991, what was the name of Live's first album?", "answers": ["Live", "Throwing Copper", "Mental Jewelry", "Cerebral Ornament"], "correctAnswer": "Mental Jewelry"},
	 		{"question":"Which band had their biggest hit with a cover of an old Louis Prima swing hit?", "answers": ["Big Bad Voodoo Daddy", "Mighty Mighty Bosstones", "Royal Crown Revue", "Royal Crown Revue"], "correctAnswer": "Royal Crown Revue"},
	 		{"question":"Puffy Daddy and The Family's hit song I'll Be Missing You is a tribute to which late rapper?", "answers": ["Notorious B.I.G.", "Tupac Shakur", "Ol' Dirty Bastard", "Eazy-E"], "correctAnswer": "Notorious B.I.G."},
	 		{"question":"Which female singer-songwriter is from Alaska?", "answers": ["Sheryl Crow", "Jewel", "Sarah McLachlan", "Alanis Morissette"], "correctAnswer": "Jewel"},
	 		{"question":"Sinead O'Connor had a hit with a cover version of Nothing Compares 2 U. Who sang it originally?", "answers": ["Prince", "Michael Jackson", "Michael Stipe", "Madonna"], "correctAnswer": "Prince"},
	 		{"question":"When you think of grunge, what city comes to mind?", "answers": ["San Diego", "Chicago", "Seattle", "New York"], "correctAnswer": "Seattle"},
	 		{"question":"Who had a one-hit wonder with the song Life is a Highway?", "answers": ["Crash Test Dummies", "Tom Cochrane", "The Verve Pipe", "Edwyn Collins"], "correctAnswer": "Tom Cochrane"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following is NOT a Dave Matthews Band song?", "answers": ["Ants Marching", "#41", "1979", "Tripping Billies"], "correctAnswer": "1979"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following is NOT the name of a Celine Dion album from the 90s?", "answers": ["The Color of My Love", "Tuesday Night Music Club", "Let's Talk About Love", "Falling into You"], "correctAnswer": "Tuesday Night Music Club"},
	 		{"question":"Charles Dickens did not write which one of the following books?", "answers": ["Barchester Towers", "Dombey and Son", "Great Expectations", "Hard Times"], "correctAnswer": "Barchester Towers"},
	 		{"question":"Which author wrote the poem that begins with 'When I was one-and-twenty/I heard a wise man say'?", "answers": ["Robert Browning", "Lewis Carroll", "A. E. Housman", "Rudyard Kipling"], "correctAnswer": "A. E. Housman"},
	 		{"question":"Of these four poets, which one was male?", "answers": ["Emily Dickinson", "Joyce Kilmer", "Amy Lowell", "Alice Duer Miller"], "correctAnswer": "Joyce Kilmer"},
	 		{"question":"According to the poem The Iliad, who or what was inside the Trojan Horse?", "answers": ["Greek Soldiers", "Trojan Soldiers", "Horses", "Nothing"], "correctAnswer": "Greek Soldiers"},
	 		{"question":"Where did the original Jezebel (shameless hussy) first appear?", "answers": ["the Bible", "a Charles Dickens story", "a Shakespearean play", "a silent film"], "correctAnswer": "the Bible"},
	 		{"question":"Who was the author of the 1978 bestseller The Ends of Power?", "answers": ["John Deal", "John Ehrlichman", "H. R. Haldeman", "Gordon Liddy"], "correctAnswer": "Gordon Liddy"},
	 		{"question":"Robert Herrick dedicated his poem that begins, 'Gather ye rosebuds while ye may', to whom?", "answers": ["farmers", "his wife", "virgins", "the king of England"], "correctAnswer": "virgins"},
	 		{"question":"Who was Hannibal Hamlin?", "answers": ["a character in Mark Twain's The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", "a character on the TV series The A Team", "a vice president under Abraham Lincoln", "the Pied Piper of a children's story "], "correctAnswer": "the Pied Piper of a children's story "},
	 		{"question":"Which of these titles were not a book written by Dr. Seuss?", "answers": ["the Cat in the Hat", "the Frog in the Bog", "Hop on Pop", "Hunches and Bunches"], "correctAnswer": "the Frog in the Bog"},
	 		{"question":"'Life is real! Life is earnest!' was the beginning of a poem written by whom?", "answers": ["Henry Wadsworth Longfellow", "Walt Whitman", "William Wordsworth", "Edgar Allen Poe"], "correctAnswer": "Henry Wadsworth Longfellow"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following books would introduce you to the crafty pirate Long John Silver", "answers": ["Captains Courageous", "Kidnapped", "Treasure Island", "Robinson Caruso"], "correctAnswer": "Treasure Island"},
	 		{"question":"'All is for the best in the best of all possible worlds' is a line from what?", "answers": ["Shakespeare's The Merchant of Venice", "Beckett's Waiting for Godot", "Voltaire's Candide", "none of the above"], "correctAnswer": "Voltaire's Candide"},
	 		{"question":"On which continent is the 1994 Disney film, 'The Lion King,' set? ", "answers": ["Asia", "Africa", "North America", "Europe"], "correctAnswer": "Africa"},
	 		{"question":"'The King of Thieves' was a straight-to-video follow up to which 1992 Disney movie? ", "answers": ["Mulan", "Pocahontas", "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", "Aladdin"], "correctAnswer": "Aladdin"},
	 		{"question":"What kind of creature is Shere Khan in the film, 'The Jungle Book'?", "answers": ["Panther", "Tiger", "Ape", "Lion"], "correctAnswer": "Tiger"},
	 		{"question":"Which 2008 Disney film tells the story of a waste robot cleaning up Earth based far in the future?", "answers": ["Ice Age", "Wall-E", "Despicable Me", "Cars"], "correctAnswer": "Wall-E"},
	 		{"question":"Which 2003 comedy film stars Queen Latifah and Steve Martin? ", "answers": ["Maid In Manhatten", "Cheaper By the Dozen", "Bringing Down the House", "Twins"], "correctAnswer": "Bringing Down the House"},
	 		{"question":"What is the occupation of C. D. Wales in the 1987 movie 'Roxanne'?", "answers": ["Politician", "Fireman", "Gangster", "Lawyer"], "correctAnswer": "Fireman"},
	 		{"question":"Which country music singer stars in the movie '9 to 5'? ", "answers": ["Reba McEntire", "Dolly Parton", "Patty Loveless", "Wynonna Judd"], "correctAnswer": "Dolly Parton"},
	 		{"question":"Select the Tom Cruise movie that was released BEFORE the others", "answers": ["The Color of Money", "Born on the Fourth of July", "Rain Man", "Cocktail"], "correctAnswer": "The Color of Money"},
	 		{"question":"What color is the lightsaber used by Yoda?", "answers": ["Yellow", "Red", "Blue", "Green"], "correctAnswer": "Green"},
	 		{"question":"What is the name of the icy planet on which the rebels have made their base in 'The Empire Strikes Back'? ", "answers": ["Loth", "Hoth", "Toth", "Goth"], "correctAnswer": "Hoth"},
	 		{"question":"Which of the following movies from 2014 was based on a 2009 James Dashner novel?", "answers": ["The Maze Runner", "The Theory of Everything", "The Equalizer", "Divergent"], "correctAnswer": "The Maze Runner"},
	 		{"question":"Complete Buzz Lightyear's catchphrase 'To Infinity and...'?", "answers": ["Away", "Fly", "Zoom", "Beyond"], "correctAnswer": "Beyond"},
	 		{"question":"What is the name of Aladdin's mischievous monkey friend?", "answers": ["Abu", "Rafiki", "Curious George", "Kong"], "correctAnswer": "Abu"}		 			 		
		]
	}

	{"category": "science",
	 "questions": [
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"},
	 		{"question":"test?", "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "correctAnswer": "d"}	 
		]
	}	

